{
  "title": "Cybersecurity - Hard Level",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which tool is typically used for enumeration in the OSINT phase of a pentest?",
      "options": [
        "Nmap",
        "Metasploit",
        "Recon-ng",
        "Wireshark"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the 'K' stand for in the cryptographic system known as RSA?",
      "options": [
        "Kryptos",
        "Kepler",
        "Kleptography",
        "Kra"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following commands would you use to display the routing table of a Unix/Linux system?",
      "options": [
        "netstat -r",
        "ipconfig /displaydns",
        "nbtstat -r",
        "arp -a"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following tools would you use to perform a DNS zone transfer?",
      "options": [
        "Nmap",
        "Dig",
        "Netcat",
        "Wireshark"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of attack involves flooding a network or system with traffic to cause a denial of service?",
      "options": [
        "DDoS attack",
        "Brute force attack",
        "SQL injection attack",
        "Cross-Site Scripting attack"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the 'cat' command do in Unix/Linux systems?",
      "options": [
        "Concatenates and displays file content",
        "Changes file permissions",
        "Changes ownership of a file",
        "Creates a new file"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the volatility tool do in the field of digital forensics?",
      "options": [
        "Recovers deleted files",
        "Analyses RAM for forensic investigations",
        "Cracks passwords",
        "Detects viruses and malware"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of a rainbow table in cryptography?",
      "options": [
        "To store keys securely",
        "To speed up the process of cracking password hashes",
        "To organize cryptographic keys by color",
        "To visualize encrypted data"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary purpose of a VPN?",
      "options": [
        "To increase your internet speed",
        "To bypass geographical restrictions",
        "To encrypt your internet traffic and enhance your online privacy",
        "To block ads and trackers"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Linux command would you use to change file permissions?",
      "options": [
        "chown",
        "chmod",
        "ls",
        "rm"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ]
}